

Luc Huynh Tan Hoang

Dob: Jan 11, 2001

Gender: Male

Phone: 0767101737

Email: hoanglhtje@gmail.com

Address: Ho Chi Minh, VietNam

CAREER OBJECTIVE

An IT professional with more than 1 year of experience seeking for becoming an IT Business Analyst to gain analytical skills and experience. At the same time contribute to the growth of the company. Become a Senior Business Analyst after 4 - 5 years.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEB 2023 - JAN 2024

BYS JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Implementation Consultant ERP

Main Responsibilities:

Conduct field surveys at factories and record factory requirements.

Gather relevant data and conduct analysis to prepare for UAT.

Exchange information inter-department, communicate efficiently with clients to find out the best solutions.

Schedule User Software Manuals and system UAT plans.

Training Users to operate the software and guide the working process between reality and the system.

Supports Error handling and system adjustment requests from Users.

Work with the Development Team and Project Manager to find the best solution according to User

Requirements.

Key Achievement:

Training for personnel at factories(Ty Lien Plastic, Nghia Son Wood, Bamboo King Vina...) to understand the working processes and tasks each person will perform.

Communicate with customers and clarify thousands of product data being managed by Excel to synchronize all data and help operate the system better.

Receive requests from users and work with the Project Manager to describe and design the best solution, hand over to the Development Team to build functions.

SEP 2022 - DEC 2022

AMIT GROUP

Business Analyst Internship

Main Responsibilities:

Write a list of questions and project quotes for clients.

Support the Project Manager in writing functional descriptions and design documents.

Support functional testing and evaluate system improvements.

Design the project wireframe using Balsamiq, Figma.

Key Achievement:

Build the "Create new exam" function by selecting available questions to create the exam as desired by the user with the support of the Project manager and Technical Leader.

Support system assessment and provide functional solutions for user convenience.

SKILLS

Knowledge Basic knowledge of Document Types: FRD, SRS, User Story.

Knowledge of Software Development Lifecycle, SQL, HTML.

Knowledge of UI/UX, UML, BPMN, Manual Testing.

Tool: Jira, Draw.IO, Figma, Balsamiq, Visual Paradigm

Soft skills	Planning, Managing daily tasks and Open-minded.
	Self-study and Active Listening, Teamwork.
	Visual Thinking and Problem-Solving skills.
EDITOATION	Ability to analyze and understand the requirements.
EDUCATION	
SEP 2019 - NOV 2023	Ho Chi Minh City Open University
	Major: Management Information System
HD12022 CED 2022	T 1 (1D : A 1 : (C) C 1(: (C 11 DAG
JUN 2023 - SEP 2023	Fundamental Business Analysis course, certificate of completion, certified by BAC.